scidev.net 2010-06-28

# SciDev.Net

## Privacy Policy

SciDev.Net is committed to providing high quality information and services about the role and impact of science and technology in the developing world. We are committed to protecting your privacy, and information will not usually be disclosed to third parties without your prior consent.  Information we collect from users of the site will be stored securely by us on computers in the UK. 

How SciDev.Net collects and uses information: 

### **Signing-up with SciDev.Net**

Signing-up with SciDev.Net means you can automatically receive our free email alerts, which feature the latest material posted on the website. You can select email options relevant to your areas of interest in English, French, Spanish or Chinese. 

We encourage our readers to express their opinions, and to facilitate this we have introduced a comment box after every article on the website. We require users of this service to sign-up with us to avoid misuse, and for comments to be personalised. 

Another key benefit offered by registration is free access to our notices service. This lets you post relevant grants, jobs, events and other announcements. The notices are included within our weekly email alerts, and therefore reach a wide audience of relevant individuals. When signing-up on the SciDev.Net website, we require some personal information, including your name, profession, country and email address. We also ask some further questions in order to gain a clearer understanding of our users as a whole. These relate to your profession and place of work. 

Your personal information is password protected for security, and you can access and change your details and requirements at any time. Signing up with SciDev.Net is free and you can unsubscribe online or by emailing support@scidev.net with your details. We reserve the right to contact you by email from time to time about our activities, or to invite you to participate in surveys to help improve our services. 

As this data is stored in the United Kingdom, you have certain rights in British law under the Data Protection Acts 1984 and 1988. In particular, you have the right to be told what personal information we hold about you on our databases. If you require further information, you should write to us, at: 

SciDev.Net   
9–11 Richmond Buildings   
London W1D 3HF  
United Kingdom

If you are concerned about how your information is used, we recommend that you review this privacy statement periodically, as SciDev.Net may update it from time to time. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at [info@scidev.net](mailto:info@scidev.net). We will be sure to address your concerns. 

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small file that contains a unique alphanumeric code selected randomly. This cookie is stored on your computer. Cookies are used, for example, to count the total number of unique users who are accessing a website over a particular period of time, or to see which pages are most frequently viewed. 

SciDev.Net's website uses cookies to collect data about its activity. Cookies do not identify the person at the computer, and information gathered is not shared with third parties. It is used to monitor the use of the website and provide us with raw data we can use to judge, and demonstrate, the website’s effectiveness.
